http://netdr.com/privacy

Viagra
Sildenafil Citrate (TP)
Tadalafil TEVA
Vardenafil TEVA
Sildenafil Citrate (GS)
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how NetDr treats personal information that is collected and received, including information related to your past use of NetDr products and services. Your personally identifiable information such as your name, address, email address, phone number and any additional information that is not otherwise public knowledge will be kept private.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that NetDr does not own or control nor to people that NetDr does not employ or manage. Information Collection stores personal information when you register with NetDr and when you order NetDr products.
When you register we ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, date of birth, gender, etc. Once you register with NetDr and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.
NetDr automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, NetDr cookie information, and the page you request.
NetDr uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research and provide anonymous reporting for internal use.
Information Sharing and Disclosure:
NetDr does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you have requested.
We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with NetDr under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help NetDr communicate with you about offers from NetDr and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information.We do respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal processes. We exercise our legal rights to defend against legal claims.
We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate,prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud or situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person as well as violations of NetDr terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
We do not transfer information about you if NetDr is acquired by or merged with another company. The new owner will not receive patient information unless they agree in writing to honor the current privacy statement of NetDr. Patients will be notified of any pending sale at least 120 days before the closing date and they may elect to have their records removed from the data base prior to closing.
NetDr displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, men ages 25-45 from a particular geographic area.
NetDr does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.
Cookies:
NetDr may set and access NetDr cookies on your computer.
NetDr lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not our policy. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to NetDr cookies.
Confidentiality and Security:
We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
Your NetDr Account Information is password-protected.
Changes to this Privacy Policy:
NetDr may update this policy. We will notify you about any significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in your NetDr account or by placing a prominent notice on our site.
Patent Pending:   60/481641
Copyright © 2020 NetDr.com. All rights reserved.
Email Us
About Us
Privacy Policy
Doctor Login
